seeknomore.blogspot.com 2015-06-01

# Seek No More: Privacy Policy

##  [Privacy Policy](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/2009/04/privacy-policy.html)

Posted by Kirhat | Wednesday, March 11, 2009 | [Privacy](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/search/label/Privacy) | [ 0 comments »](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/2009/04/privacy-policy.html#comment-form)

The author added the blog’s privacy policy in compliance with the requirements set by Google Adsense for publishers running interest-based ads. The modification in policy includes the inclusion of a link to the Google ad and content network policy.

This is the new privacy policy:

At [Seek No More](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/), the privacy of blog visitors is of extreme importance the author. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by [Seek No More](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/) and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, [Seek No More](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. [Seek No More](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [Seek No More](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[Seek No More](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [Seek No More](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/) privacy policy does not apply to, and it cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please contact the author by filling up the [contact form](http://seeknomore.blogspot.com/2007/08/contact-us.html).
